[Music]
Elevate Healthcare Story
A beautiful family Srinivas Lakshmi
and their little boy Rohan
were always happy but
they had a little worry about the future.
One day, while Srinivas was thinking about health insurance,
he came across the Elevate policy
.  This is from ICICI Lombard
General Insurance.  They were surprised to learn that this
policy coverage ranges from 5 lakhs to unlimited
.   This
means that no matter how large the amount, there will be protection.  Srinivas was very happy when he heard about the Infinite Care addon
.  This
allows for an unlimited claim once.
Lakshmi
really liked the idea of ​​Infinite Assurance on your Sum Insured.  With Jump Start,
pre-existing conditions are also covered from the 31st day
.  This is really a big relief.
They learned that even a two-hour hospitalization is considered inpatient treatment, and that costs are covered for 90 days before hospitalization and 180 days after discharge from the hospital.  It is very
comfortable.  They also learned that their children are considered
dependents until they turn 30
and the policy can be taken from the age of 18
.  This is a
great assurance for their family's future. They immediately decided to contact Anand Kumar after learning that there were additional benefits such as
premium discounts based on credit score,
early renewal discounts, and
discounts on long-term policies of two to three years
.
Anand Kumar explained all the details
clearly to them.  With their number 9 1 6 0
2 4 3
4 6
Elevate policy, the Srinivas family is
now
living happily without any worries about the future.
Please note that if you
have already taken a policy from ICICI Lombard, those
details
will not be available with Anand Kumar.
Contact only for new Elevate policy.